## **Jordan Alexis**

alexisjordan842@gmail.com ● alexisjordan842@yahoo.com ● (646) 625-8972 ● Brooklyn, NY

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer | Computer Programmer | Web Designer | Office Clerk | Data Analyst

Executing the Day → Planning the Future → Impacting Results →

Watching the Bottom Line → Solving Issues → Supporting Teams → Serving Clients → Cleaning

Data

- I have experience using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Cloud Computing, and others to help build websites for clients or myself.
- Experience using Adobe Creative Cloud applications such as Premiere, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, and XD to help make my websites and other jobs I must do.
- Experience entering client information into a database and checking that the data is secured and correct. Dealing with customers who need help with orders placed and account information.

Skills		Speciali	Specializations	
Office Management	Calendar Management	Relationship Development	Training   Development	
Client Relations	Project Management	Adobe XD, Dreamweaver,	Benefit Administration	
Form Processing	Research	Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat,	MS Office, Word, Excel,	
Social Media-	Data-driven Analysis	Premiere.	Outlook, PowerPoint	
Manager	Accts Payable/Receivable	Hootsuite	HTML/CSS, PHP,	
Office Planning	Data Analytics	Visual Studios Code	Responsive Design,	
		Eclipse	jQuery	
		GitHub		

## **Professional Experience**

B&A Appliances – Brooklyn, NY Data Entry Associate

Jan 2020 - Present

**SNAPSHOT:** Reported to the owner of B&A. Accurately entering and updating customer information in the company database. Managing inventory data, ensuring up-to-date and precise records. Addressed customer inquiries and resolved complaints, ensuring high customer satisfaction.

- Processed sales transactions, handled cash, and managed POS systems.
- Addressed customer inquiries and resolved complaints, ensuring high customer satisfaction.

Tip Top Shoes – Manhattan, NY Product Lister and Data Entry Dec 2023 - Dec 2023

**SNAPSHOT:** Reported to the Sales Representative of Tip Top Shoes. Edited product, and category details, including product listings, images, and prices that became published on their Shopify websites and other Social Media portals. Followed the standards and best practices for new product listings, page creation, and interlinking.

- Optimized images of products for the site.
- Maintained the Database where the information needed to be stored.

#### **Unadat – Manhattan, NY Software Engineer Intern**

July 2021 – Aug 2021

**SNAPSHOT:** Reported to the Executive Director of Unadat. Managed a cross-functional team to develop a dark mode for the Unadat portal site. Supported operations through data-driven analysis and people metric reporting. Collaborated with the design team in devising and user-testing the color scheme and functionality.

- Optimized dark theme for the mobile and progressive web app.
- Debugged independent research to overcome roadblocks and obstacles.

#### WBAI Radio 99.5FM NYC - Brooklyn, NY **Spring Intern**

Jan 2019 - May 2019

SNAPSHOT: Reported to Director of Development. Provided support with keeping up with the shows and events through social media posts and the Event Calendar. Provided customer service to the listeners, helped with the support of the "BAI Buddies" (membership that the supporters of the station were called), mail-in prizes that they won, and merchandise they brought from the website or on-call.

- Organized the photos and the text that the event calendar and social media had.
- Handled social media from February to May

#### The Challenge Publisher Group - Brooklyn, NY Multimedia Internship

July 2018 - Aug 2018

SNAPSHOT: Reported to the Organizer of the Group. Managed the project to get the newspaper "The New American" into the modern age using Adobe InDesign. She distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York using email and placing the papers in mailboxes.

• Creating a timeline to show where the project would be by the end of the internship.

#### Brooklyn Neighborhood Improvement Association (BNIA) – Brooklyn, NY Office Assistant | Intern

Aug 2017 – Aug 2017

SNAPSHOT: Reported to the director of BNIA. Provided support for the Summer Youth Interns by connecting them to their site providers. Helped with entering the work hours that the interns had on their timesheets and ensuring that the interns were not casing any disruptive actions that would impede the workflow of the site.

## St. John's Recreation Center - Brooklyn, NY

July 2017 - Aug 2017

#### Multimedia Developer Internship.

SNAPSHOT: Reported to the site provider. Learned how Adobe products operated and assisted other students with any issues using the Adobe system. Hands-on experience with a radio room and learning the basics of audio and video production.

# Charles Churn Christian Academy - Brooklyn, NY

July 2014 to Aug 2014

## **Day Care Worker**

**SNAPSHOT:** Reported to the Site Manager. Assisted in creating and providing activities for the kids. Helped carry 5-20 pounds of equipment/bags to the trips they went on—support of keeping them out of harm's way.

#### **Education**

**Bachelor's Degree, Multimedia Computing and Information Science** - Brooklyn College, Brooklyn, NY, Aug 2019 - Present

**Associate degree, Multimedia Programming, and Design** - Borough of Manhattan Community College, Manhattan, NY, Aug 2017 – May 2019

Credits Towards Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications: Associate degree - Technical Career Institute, Manhattan, NY, Jan 2017 – May 2017

Credits Towards Computer Information Systems (Game Design Concertation): Associate degree Bramson Ort College, Queens NY, Oct 2014 – Jan 2017